<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_about/</guid>
      <description>The services Test automation framework implementations. Guidance on testing process within the CI/CD pipelines. Cross-team testing strategies. Accessibility audits for web and mobile app. Book an intro meeting</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-services">The services</h2>
<ul>
<li>Test automation framework implementations.</li>
<li>Guidance on testing process within the CI/CD pipelines.</li>
<li>Cross-team testing strategies.</li>
<li>Accessibility audits for web and mobile app.</li>
</ul>
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<p><a href="https://calendly.com/jaffamonkeyltd/intro-call">Book an intro meeting</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessbility and autism</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_autism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_autism/</guid>
      <description>Autism is a spectrum. Not everyone who is autistic prefers the same things. Many autistic people also have associated other conditions, like Dyslexia or Learning Difficulties thatimpact on their preferences. Many do not have other conditions. Other demographic factors can also impact people’s references, such as socio economic factors, and familiarity with technology.&#xA;These differences can make it challenging to design for all autistic web users, and below is a general guide to assist in those challenges.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Autism is a spectrum. Not everyone who is autistic prefers the same things. Many autistic people also have associated other conditions, like Dyslexia or Learning Difficulties thatimpact on their preferences. Many do not have other conditions. Other demographic factors can also impact people’s references, such as socio economic factors, and familiarity with technology.</p>
<p>These differences can make it challenging to design for all autistic web users, and below is a general guide to assist in those challenges.</p>
<h2 id="page-design">Page Design</h2>
<h3 id="background-images">Background images</h3>
<ul>
<li>Background images have to have a purpose. Geometric shapes in muted colours
work well but image collages are considered distracting.</li>
<li>For autistic web users they can struggle to distinguish between foreground and background.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="symmetry-in-design">Symmetry in design</h3>
<ul>
<li>There was a general preference for symmetry in design and for clearly defined sections
including images having clear boarders.</li>
<li>Symmetrically designed webpages were considered</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="logical-ordering">Logical ordering</h3>
<ul>
<li>All users expected some logical ordering of information on webpages – for example,importance (where the most important information is on top), alphabetical (lists), or chronological (in forums).</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="logical-sizing-of-elements">Logical sizing of elements</h3>
<ul>
<li>Generally, participants associated the size of design elements (e.g. boxes)
with the importance of information/content presented in those areas.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="no-auto-playing-contentmovement">No auto-playing content/movement</h3>
<ul>
<li>Moving adverts in banners and pop-ups, auto-playing videos make websites inaccessible to most autistic web users.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="no-surprises">No surprises</h3>
<ul>
<li>Avoid unpredictable situations and changes. This includes changing designs of websites that they used.</li>
<li>Preview should be available with information on what pages, sections and videos are about before reading/watching them.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="page-layout">Page Layout</h2>
<h3 id="design-clear-clutter-free-pages">Design clear, clutter-free pages</h3>
<ul>
<li>Build simple pages that include only elements relevant to the current user task</li>
<li>Cluttered, busy layouts make finding information difficult and do not
allow users to focus on their core tasks.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="set-page-lengths-appropriately-to-the-page-type--function">Set page lengths appropriately to the page type &amp; function</h3>
<ul>
<li>Make decisions about the length of the page appropriately to its purpose. For
example, make your homepage short and ensure that important information &amp; sections are
available with minimum scrolling. Content pages, e.g. article pages may be longer to
facilitate uninterrupted reading.</li>
<li>Homepages that are too long do not allow users to focus on their core tasks and make
finding information difficult.</li>
<li>Too much scrolling makes autistic users feel ‘dizzy’ and ‘overwhelmed’.</li>
<li>On long pages, users can feel like they are lost in “something” that has no end.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="clearly-separate-design-elements--sections-that-do-not-belongtogether">Clearly separate design elements &amp; sections that do not belongtogether</h3>
<ul>
<li>Clearly separate different sections and items on the page by using white space
(i.e. space without text or graphics), outlines, boarders and dividers (i.e. lines) to help users</li>
<li>All design elements should have clearly defined outlines and boarders to be
able to focus on them, as well as to move between the different sections within the page. Lack of clear outlines can make vision blur.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="place-important-information-on-top-of-the-page-and-above-the-fold">Place important information on top of the page and above the fold</h3>
<ul>
<li>Whenever possible, establish a high-to-low hierarchy of importance of items on
the page.</li>
<li>Place the information that is most important for users on top of the page above
the fold.</li>
<li>For items of equal importance, use alphabetical listing, or chronological ordering
(e.g. forum threads, event timelines).</li>
<li>Users look for the most important information on top of the page above the fold.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-the-size-of-design-elements-to-communicate-the-importance-of-information-that-they-carry">Use the size of design elements to communicate the importance of information that they carry</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use the size of design elements (e.g. larger boxes) to help users find
important information easily.</li>
<li>Users judge the importance of information by the size of the boxes that carry
the information, i.e. the content in larger boxes is more important than information in
smaller boxes.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="avoid-large-images-above-the-fold">Avoid large images above the fold</h3>
<ul>
<li>Avoid large images that would cover the entire space above the fold,
if there is more information below the fold.</li>
<li>Users were overwhelmed by large banners that covered most of the space above the
fold blocking their way to information below it.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="for-each-page-provide-a-summary-of-the-page--its-purpose">For each page, provide a summary of the page &amp; its purpose</h3>
<p>Provide a short descriptive summary of the page to help users to understand
the topic and purpose of this page. This includes the homepage.
Users want to know what pages and sections of the website they are on and often the page titles are not descriptive enough to provide this information. Autistic users feel disorientated when this information is not available and are likely to leave the site.</p>
<h3 id="ensure-the-consistency-of-page-layout-using-symmetry">Ensure the consistency of page layout using symmetry</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that design elements are aligned and laid out symmetrically on the page.
Whenever possible, maintain an equal number of columns on the page.</li>
<li>Autistic users have a strong preference for symmetrically designed pages. Pages where visual elements (e.g. boxes or images) should ne aligned, and there are an equal number of columns in sections across the page.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="maintain-a-visual-consistency-of-design-elements-within-a-single-section-of-the-page">Maintain a visual consistency of design elements within a single section of the page</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that the shape of design elements within a single section of the page are
visually consistent.</li>
<li>Consistent visual design of elements grouped together in a container element, e.g. only boxes with rounded corners, or only boxes with square corners, but not both in the same section of the page.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="navigation">Navigation</h2>
<h3 id="design-consistent--simple-navigation-across-the-site">Design consistent &amp; simple navigation across the site</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that the navigation across the site is consistent and allows users to
understand how they can navigate to different pages &amp; sections on the site.</li>
<li>Websites with complex and inconsistent navigation make people use Google and
deep-link directly to the content. It also leads people away from the website as there may be other websites with similar content listed higher on the search pages. In the survey, confusing navigation was one of the main problems experienced online by autistic respondents.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="ensure-that-all-links-and-buttons-are-visibly-clickable">Ensure that all links and buttons are visibly clickable</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that links are clearly visible and distinct from other text and non-clickable
elements, by using colour and underlining. Apply the design consistently across the site.</li>
<li>Autistic users expect links (including visited links) to be both underlined and differ in
colour from other text &amp; non-clickable elements.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="ensure-that-users-understand-how-to-navigate-carousels">Ensure that users understand how to navigate carousels</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that users understand which element on the page is a carousel and how
they can access the multiple carousel panels. Make the navigation arrows clearly visible and
provide information about the number of panels in the carousel</li>
<li>Some of the less web-savvy users miss the arrows on the carousel, until prompted
to look for them. Some people do not want to interact with the carousel until they had information about the number of available panels.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-sequential-menus-with-fewer-items-to-select">Use sequential menus with fewer items to select</h3>
<ul>
<li>Design menus with fewer options that enable users to easily make selection</li>
<li>On-hover menus, as well as menus that include too many items discourage autistic
people from using the site. Sequential menus with fewer options that allow “pointing and clicking” rather than “mousing-over” work better for autistic users.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-a-sticky-main-menu">Use a sticky main menu</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use a sticky main menu on the top of the page, to enable users to easily navigate
to any other section of the website. Avoid other sticky design elements on the site, e.g. adverts</li>
<li>Autistic users said that they liked to always have access to other sections of the site
and a sticky main menu facilitated this. They found other sticky design elements on the page
distracting, e.g. sticky advert banners, sticky side nav with links to related content, or icons for content sharing.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="colours">Colours</h2>
<h3 id="avoid-using-lots-of-bright-colours-on-the-website">Avoid using lots of bright colours on the website</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use simple, soft colours and colour combinations for the background, logo,
images and text across the website. Autistic users prefer low-contrast colour schemes.</li>
<li>Bright contrasting colours are commonly known to be visually overstimulating. 64% of
survey respondents agreed that they got distracted by bright colours. 69% of respondents find
bright images distracting. (See also Guideline 3.2.)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="allow-users-to-customise-the-background--text-colours">Allow users to customise the background &amp; text colours</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to choose the background and text colours that suit their needs.</li>
<li>There is no standard autistic colour preference.</li>
<li>Being able to choose their colours on the web would significantly improve user experience.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="fonts">Fonts</h2>
<h3 id="choose-a-typeface-for-your-website-and-use-it-consistently">Choose a typeface for your website and use it consistently</h3>
<h3 id="use-at-least-12pt-font-across-the-website">Use at least 12pt font across the website</h3>
<ul>
<li>To ensure readability of text on the site, use a font size not smaller than 12 pt.</li>
<li>Generally, users prefer larger size fonts, at least 12 pt.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="choose-a-typeface-for-your-website-and-use-it-consistently-1">Choose a typeface for your website and use it consistently.</h3>
<ul>
<li>Avoid using serif &amp; sans-serif fonts on the same page</li>
<li>Avoid using too many typefaces on the site. Use consistently either a serif
or a sans-serif font across your website. Avoid using both a serif font &amp; a sans-serif font
on the same page.</li>
<li>Some autistic users prefer sans-serif fonts, while others read better in serif fonts.
Autistic users feel distracted when both type of fonts are used on the same page.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="allow-users-to-customise-the-font-type--size-to-suit-their-needs">Allow users to customise the font type &amp; size to suit their needs</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to choose the font type &amp; size that best suit their needs, in order to
make reading easier for them</li>
<li>Autistic users have different preferences regarding the use of serif and sans-serif fonts,
and font sizes.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="text">Text</h2>
<h3 id="ensure-sufficient-spacing-between-paragraphs-and-between-linesof-text">Ensure sufficient spacing between paragraphs and between linesof text</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use white space (areas not filled with text or graphics) consistently to separate paragraphs and lines of text</li>
<li>All users but particularly users with associated learning disabilities (those with “eye-
tracking” issues). People with ADHD find densely spaced text difficult to read</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="organise-text-into-short-paragraphs-and-use-short-lines">Organise text into short paragraphs and use short lines</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use short paragraphs and short lines to organise the text for easier reading</li>
<li>Users found long paragraphs and long lines difficult to read.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="do-not-interrupt-the-flow-of-text-with-images-or-other-designelements">Do not interrupt the flow of text with images or other designelements</h3>
<ul>
<li>Avoid splitting the text with elements that may interrupt the flow of reading. Avoid
scroll-stoppers that may mislead users into thinking that they have reached the end of the text
when they have not.</li>
<li>Users want to be able to read the text without interruption. Large images or video
content placed in the text interrupt users’ thought process. It is worse when the design element fills up a large part of the screen.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="avoid-using-bold-text-style-for-large-amounts-of-text-and-in-combination-with-other-text-styles">Avoid using bold text style for large amounts of text and in combination with other text styles</h3>
<ul>
<li>Limit the use of bold text to highlight keywords or important phrases in the text to make them stand out to readers</li>
<li>Applying bolding to a large amount of text confuses users and makes them feel
agitated.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="bold-the-keywords-to-facilitate-rapid-scanning-of-text-for-important-information">Bold the keywords to facilitate rapid scanning of text for important information</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use bold text to draw user’s attention to keywords or important phrases in the text</li>
<li>Bold text helps readers to scan text for important information.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="non-textual-formats">Non-textual formats</h2>
<h3 id="consider-providing-information-in-video-format">Consider providing information in video format</h3>
<ul>
<li>Consider providing information in video format with captions &amp; transcripts</li>
<li>THis will make it easier for users to process and remember information
from video than from text only. Most users also find captions and transcripts for videos useful.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-visuals-with-the-text-to-facilitate-understanding">Use visuals with the text to facilitate understanding</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use visuals to facilitate understanding of textual information and to help users
locate required information on the page.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-icons-to-help-users-locate-information-faster">Use icons to help users locate information faster</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use meaningful &amp; memorable icons to help users find information on the page</li>
<li>Autistic users find icons helpful when scanning web pages for information, especially
on busy text-heavy pages where there were many visually similar sections, e.g. laid-out in a grid.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="images">Images</h2>
<h3 id="use-simple-images-that-can-be-easily-understood">Use simple images that can be easily understood</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use simple images that can be understood at “a glance”, without a need for a deep visual analysis.</li>
<li>Users want images that are simple and easy to understand. Users found images
showing a single object in focus easier to process.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-meaningful-relatable-images-that-add-value--clarity-to-the-information-on-the-page">Use meaningful, relatable images that add value &amp; clarity to the information on the page</h3>
<ul>
<li>Make sure your images are meaningful and add value &amp; clarity to the text
information on the page</li>
<li>Autistic users wanted images to be meaningful and congruent with the story on the
page. Images must add value, provide more information or clarification to the text, represent
information visually (e.g. infographics).</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="limit-the-use-of-background-images-and-decorative-graphics">Limit the use of background images and decorative graphics</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use background images sparingly, especially if they are overlaid with text. If you use
decorative graphics, ensure they do not distract the users from reading text.
Use non-patterned backgrounds on content pages to facilitate uninterrupted reading.</li>
<li>Autistic users find background images and decorative graphics distracting, They
preferred plain background, especially on content pages where there is much textual information to read through.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-photographs-of-people-only-if-depicted-people-are-relevant-to-the-information">Use photographs of people only if depicted people are relevant to the information</h3>
<ul>
<li>Use photographs of people only if these people are relevant to the story</li>
<li>Text-first autistic users found generic photos of people irritating and irrelevant</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="provide-the-ability-to-turn-off-decorative-graphics--all-images">Provide the ability to turn off decorative graphics &amp; all images</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to turn off decorative graphics &amp; all images on the website to enable
them to focus on textual information.</li>
<li>Text-first users find all images distracting and would benefit from an ability to turn all
graphics off or on.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="video-and-audio">Video and audio</h2>
<h3 id="disable-auto-play">Disable auto-play</h3>
<ul>
<li>Do not make video content to auto-play on pages, even if the sound is off. Users
prefer control over what content is playing and when it is playing.</li>
<li>If you include auto-play there was must be an option to turn it off.</li>
<li>Auto-playing videos made users feel “nervous” and “out of control” over their online
experience. They wanted to be able to decide what and when they want to watch or listen to.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="video-content">Video Content</h2>
<h3 id="provide-captions-for-videos-and-transcripts-for-all-video--audio-content">Provide captions for videos and transcripts for all video &amp; audio content</h3>
<ul>
<li>Provide captions for all videos. Provide transcripts for video and audio to enable
text-first users to access the same information in text format.</li>
<li>Captions help Text-first users to access information available in video format.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="allow-users-to-turn-off-captions">Allow users to turn off captions</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to switch captions off according to their preferences</li>
<li>Some visual autistic users find captions distracting and would like to be able to turn
them off (i.e. they prefer closed captions to open captions).</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="provide-text-based-introductory-information-for-videos-on-pages">Provide text-based introductory information for videos on pages</h3>
<ul>
<li>Provide text-based introductory information for videos so that users can read it
before they play the content</li>
<li>Before they decide to play video content, users wanted to know what the video was
about and how long it was.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="use-video-content-when-it-adds-value-or-increases-clarity-of-textual-information-on-the-site">Use video content when it adds value or increases clarity of textual information on the site</h3>
<ul>
<li>Make sure video content adds value and increases clarity of textual information on
the site</li>
<li>Video content can be a distraction to users, including visual users, therefore, videos
must add value to the site and focus on explaining information presented in the text.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="movement">Movement</h2>
<h3 id="disable-auto-playing-movement-on-pages">Disable auto-playing movement on pages.</h3>
<h3 id="provide-a-pause-mechanism">Provide a pause mechanism</h3>
<h3 id="avoid-attention-attracting-movement-unless-other-methods-of-visual-emphasis-have-failed">Avoid attention-attracting movement unless other methods of visual emphasis have failed</h3>
<h3 id="disable-auto-playing-movement-on-pages-1">Disable auto-playing movement on pages.</h3>
<ul>
<li>Provide a pause mechanism for moving &amp; animated design elements (e.g. carousels)</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="avoid-using-pop-ups-moving-or-animated-design-elements-if-eliminating-movement-is">Avoid using pop-ups, moving or animated design elements. If eliminating movement is</h3>
<p>impossible, provide a pause mechanism to “return” control to users.</p>
<ul>
<li>Even the smallest movement can have negative impact on some autistic web users.</li>
<li>Auto-playing carousels should be avoided as can be difficult to read the text before the panels change.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="avoid-attention-attracting-movement-unless-other-methods-of">Avoid attention-attracting movement unless other methods of</h3>
<p>visual emphasis have failed</p>
<ul>
<li>Small animated movement may be used to draw users’ attention to information or to invite
users to take action if all other methods of visual emphasis such as: size, colour, font style, have failed.</li>
<li>Small animated movement of an arrow when moused-over, communicated to users that the section
was clickable and more information was available. This movement was limited and explainable, and users did not find it disturbing.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="help-pages">Help pages</h2>
<h3 id="provide-help-on-the-website-in-a-range-of-formats">Provide help on the website in a range of formats</h3>
<ul>
<li>Ensure that all autistic users are effectively supported when problems occur on
the site. Provide help for your website in a range of formats &amp; channels, e.g. via phone or a
live chat, as well as via email and on the site (via FAQ pages).</li>
<li>Some autistic users prefer to use the phone or a live chat to access help on the site quickly.
People with phone anxiety tend to look for answers on the site, e.g. FAQ pages, Google, or want to be able to send their queries via email.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="forms">Forms</h2>
<h3 id="use-clear-unique-labels--instructions-for-each-field">Use clear, unique labels &amp; instructions for each field</h3>
<ul>
<li>When designing forms, use unique labels and clearly explain what information
needs to be entered</li>
<li>Autistic users struggled with labels that were ambiguous or similar to other labels. For example, they found “username” and “sign-in name” confusing, and were unsure about these different names would used on a site.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="ensure-reasonable-timeouts">Ensure reasonable timeouts</h3>
<ul>
<li>When using forms with an authentication timeout, ensure that the timeout is
reasonable and sufficient for users to complete the form. Warn users about the expiring
timeout and provide means to extend the session time limit.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="provide-immediate-feedback-on-errors">Provide immediate feedback on errors</h3>
<ul>
<li>Provide immediate feedback to allow users to quickly realise when they made an
error when filling in the form</li>
<li>Form errors should provide mmediate feedback to be able to correct errors promptly when
they’ve occurred.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="use-of-language">Use of language</h2>
<h3 id="use-clear-precise-language-and-avoid-metaphors--ambiguous-terms">Use clear, precise language and avoid metaphors &amp; ambiguous terms</h3>
<ul>
<li>Autistic users want information to be delivered in concise and “to the point” manner.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="use-of-language-1">Use of language</h2>
<h3 id="avoid-jargon-abbreviations-acronyms-idioms--colloquialisms">Avoid jargon, abbreviations, acronyms, idioms &amp; colloquialisms</h3>
<ul>
<li>Avoid using specialist niche terminology or colloquial language on the site.</li>
<li>Use clear and concise language that is familiar to users</li>
<li>Users struggle with understanding specialist terminology or colloquial language.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="customisation">Customisation</h2>
<h3 id="allow-users-to-customise-the-website--make-customisation-clearly-available">Allow users to customise the website &amp; make customisation clearly available</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to tailor their experience on the website to their needs &amp;
preferences.</li>
<li>Essential customisation must include tools to change font type &amp; size, text &amp;
background colours, an ability to turn off decorative graphics, an ability to turn off captions
for video content.</li>
<li>Available accessibility tools must be clearly visible &amp; easy to use.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="sharing-content">Sharing content</h2>
<h3 id="allow-users-to-share-content-via-e-mail--platforms-that-they-use">Allow users to share content via e-mail &amp; platforms that they use</h3>
<ul>
<li>Allow users to share content from the website via social media platforms
that they use, and enable them to e-mail content to others and to themselves for ‘slow’
reading.</li>
<li>Autistic web users wanted to be able to share content from websites on social media
platforms that they used.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="re-learnability">Re-learnability</h2>
<h3 id="communicate-your-plans-about-changes-on-the-website-clearly--in-advance">Communicate your plans about changes on the website clearly &amp; in advance</h3>
<ul>
<li>Announce any planned changes on your website in advance, inform the users
about what is going to change and when the changes are going to be implemented.</li>
<li>Change disorientates users. Users can feel lost and frustrated when the websites that they
like and use change frequently or unexpectedly.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessbility Strategy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_accessibilitystrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_accessibilitystrategy/</guid>
      <description>Understanding why accessibility makes you a better and smarter organisation is the first step in any long-term strategy.&#xA;What are advantage of integrating Accessibility into your design and development practices.&#xA;Drive Innovation Accessibility features in products and services often solve unanticipated problems.&#xA;Enhance Your Brand Diversity and inclusion efforts so important to business success are accelerated with a clear, well-integrated accessibility commitment.&#xA;Extend Market Reach The global market of people with disabilities is over 1 billion people with a spending power of more than $6 trillion.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Understanding why accessibility makes you a better and smarter organisation is the first step in any long-term strategy.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>What are advantage of integrating Accessibility into your design and development practices.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="drive-innovation">Drive Innovation</h2>
<p>Accessibility features in products and services often solve unanticipated problems.</p>
<h2 id="enhance-your-brand">Enhance Your Brand</h2>
<p>Diversity and inclusion efforts so important to business success are accelerated with a clear, well-integrated accessibility commitment.</p>
<h2 id="extend-market-reach">Extend Market Reach</h2>
<p>The global market of people with disabilities is over 1 billion people with a spending power of more than $6 trillion. Accessibility often improves the online experience for all users.</p>
<h2 id="minimize-legal-risk">Minimize Legal Risk</h2>
<p>Many countries have laws requiring digital accessibility, and the issue is of increased legal concern.</p>
<p><a href="https://calendly.com/jaffamonkeyltd/intro-call">Book an intro meeting</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility audit</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_accessibilityaudit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_accessibilityaudit/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility means more than putting things online. It means making your content and design clear and simple enough so that most people can use it without needing to adapt it, while supporting those who do need to adapt things.” GOV.UK (2019 - Understanding new accessibility requirements for public sector bodies)&#xA;Get an audit at any point in your project, and also get advice with pushing accessibility as part of your way of working, from design to code to production</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>Accessibility means more than putting things online.
It means making your content and design clear and simple enough so that most people can use it without needing to adapt it, while supporting those who do need to adapt things.”
GOV.UK (2019 - Understanding new accessibility
requirements for public sector bodies)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Get an audit at any point in your project, and also get advice with pushing accessibility as part of your way of working, from design to code to production</p>
<p>The audit targets a wide range of disabilities, including visual, auditory, physical, speech, cognitive, language, learning, and neurological disabilities.</p>
<p>Professionally evaluating the website&rsquo;s accessibility level is a key step in web accessibility and can be performed at any stage of a web or mobile app project.</p>
<h2 id="advantages">Advantages</h2>
<p>Our services are cost-effective and efficient, ensuring that businesses of all sizes can afford and benefit from our expertise.</p>
<p>Additionally, our in-depth knowledge and experience in web accessibility and WCAG compliance allow us to deliver exceptional results and ensure that our clients&rsquo; digital content is accessible to all users.</p>
<p>Furthermore, our focus on DevOps integration is a unique aspect of our consultancy services.</p>
<p>This integration of accessibility practises into the development workflow gives our clients a significant advantage in creating inclusive digital experiences.</p>
<h2 id="what-you-will-get">What you will get</h2>
<ul>
<li>A full accessibility review and test of web or mobile app against the WCAG 2.2 AA standard.</li>
<li>Delivery of a full, prioritised accessibility report of web and/or mobile app</li>
<li>We’ll test with assistive technologies to aid the results</li>
<li>An accessibility statement (inline with your current accessibility status) that can be published to a website advising on status of WCAG 2.2 AA compliance.</li>
<li>Automated accessibility test framework for your CI pipeline</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>Treat an audit as a startpoint, to integrating accessibility checks earlier in the development lifecycle.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="the-process">The process</h2>
<h3 id="questions">Questions</h3>
<ul>
<li>Is the audit for web and/or mobile app?</li>
<li>What is WCAG Level Required?</li>
<li>Do you have User guides?</li>
<li>Do we need login details?</li>
<li>For web, do you have a sitemap.xml or list opf URLs?</li>
<li>For mobile app, do you have a template list&quot;</li>
<li>Do you need Extended UX checks (disability-focused)</li>
<li>Is access to source control possible?</li>
<li>Do you need more customised test automation scripting (to follow user journeys, for example)</li>
<li>Do you need tools integrations into design and development environment</li>
<li>Do you need an Accessibility strategy from design/development perspective.</li>
<li>DO you need Web based dashboard where you can add/maintain new URL&rsquo;s for regular checks and monitoring.</li>
<li>Do you need code-level checking and reporting (SonarQube)</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="recent-clients">Recent clients</h2>
<ul>
<li>Coloplast</li>
<li>HealthwaveHub</li>
<li>Infervision</li>
<li>TympaHealth</li>
<li>ZoomDoc</li>
<li>Medialogix</li>
<li>IMS Maxims</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility statement</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_accessibilitystatement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_accessibilitystatement/</guid>
      <description>This accessibility statement applies to jaffamonkey Ltd website.&#xA;This website is run by jaffamonkey Ltd. We want as many people as possible to be able to use this website. For example, that means you should be able to:&#xA;change colours, contrast levels and fonts using browser or device settings zoom in up to 200% without the text spilling off the screen navigate most of the website using a keyboard or speech recognition software listen to most of the website using a screen reader (including NVDA and VoiceOver) We’ve also made the website text as simple as possible to understand.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p><strong>This accessibility statement applies to jaffamonkey Ltd website.</strong></p>
</blockquote>
<p>This website is run by jaffamonkey Ltd. We want as many people as possible to be able to use this website. For example, that means you should be able to:</p>
<ul>
<li>change colours, contrast levels and fonts using browser or device settings</li>
<li>zoom in up to 200% without the text spilling off the screen</li>
<li>navigate most of the website using a keyboard or speech recognition software</li>
<li>listen to most of the website using a screen reader (including NVDA and VoiceOver)</li>
<li>We’ve also made the website text as simple as possible to understand.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="how-accessible-this-website-is">How accessible this website is</h2>
<p>This site is compliant with WCAG 2.2 Level AA guidelines</p>
<h3 id="feedback-and-contact-information">Feedback and contact information</h3>
<p>If you find any problems not listed on this page or think we’re not meeting accessibility requirements, contact us.</p>
<p>If you need information on this website in a different format like accessible PDF, large print, easy read, audio recording or braille:
Email <a href="mailto:paullittlebury@gmail.com">paullittlebury@gmail.com</a> and we’ll consider your request and get back to you in 3 days.</p>
<h2 id="enforcement-procedure">Enforcement procedure</h2>
<p>The Equality and Human Rights Commission (EHRC) is responsible for enforcing the Public Sector Bodies (Websites and Mobile Applications) (No. 2) Accessibility Regulations 2018 (the ‘accessibility regulations’). If you’re not happy with how we respond to your complaint, contact the Equality Advisory and Support Service (EASS).</p>
<h2 id="technical-information-about-this-websites-accessibility">Technical information about this website’s accessibility</h2>
<p>jaffamonkey Ltd is committed to making its website accessible, in accordance with the Public Sector Bodies (Websites and Mobile Applications) (No. 2) Accessibility Regulations 2018.</p>
<h2 id="compliance-status">Compliance status</h2>
<p>This website is fully compliant with the [Web Content Accessibility Guidelines version 2.1 AA standard or Web Content Accessibility Guidelines version 2.2 AA standard].</p>
<h2 id="preparation-of-this-accessibility-statement">Preparation of this accessibility statement</h2>
<p>It is recommended that an audit be carried out following a substantial revision to your website. The statement must also be updated.</p>
<p>The statement must be reviewed at least once a year, even if there have not been significant changes to the website. Include the date of the last review.]</p>
<p>This statement was prepared on 30/10/2023. It was last reviewed on 29/10/2023.</p>
<p>This website was last tested on 29/10/2023 using:</p>
<ul>
<li>Pa11y tools. <a href="https://github.com/pa11y">Pa11y on Github</a></li>
<li>Screenreader automation. <a href="https://github.com/guidepup">Guidepup on Github</a></li>
<li>Manual checks on desktop/mobile views.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Career history</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_history/</guid>
      <description>Download Word Version&#xA;I combine the disciplines of test engineering, DevOps, exploratory testing, test management and quality assurance to provide a more rounded contribution than simply testing. 10 years total commercial experience of building test frameworks and coding API, UI and performance tests. Ensuring maximum value, by implementing tests in CI/CD pipelines. Expertise in challenging environments, and contributing improvements to the process of achieving testing goals and objectives. Frequently involved in DevOps and business decisions, and have mentored both technical and business members of team, to engage more with the quality process.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://jaffamonkey.com/img/clients.png" alt="Client history"></p>
<p><a href="https://jaffamonkey.com/img/paul-littlebury-cv.docx">Download Word Version</a></p>
<p>I combine the disciplines of test engineering, DevOps, exploratory testing, test management and quality assurance to provide a more rounded contribution than simply testing. 10 years total commercial experience of building test frameworks and coding API, UI and performance tests. Ensuring maximum value, by implementing tests in CI/CD pipelines. Expertise in challenging environments, and contributing improvements to the process of achieving testing goals and objectives. Frequently involved in DevOps and business decisions, and have mentored both technical and business members of team, to engage more with the quality process.</p>
<h1 id="highlights">Highlights</h1>
<ul>
<li>Experience in test engineering in multiple languages</li>
<li>Leading teams in adopting quality as part of way of working.</li>
<li>Mentoring less experienced testers in test engineering.</li>
<li>Extensive experience in web and mobile test automation.</li>
<li>Working with Development and DevOps teams to improve CI.</li>
<li>Involving the business more directly with quality process.</li>
<li>Proactively promoting quality as means to measure success.</li>
<li>Introducing non-functional testing as standard practice.</li>
<li>Agile, Scrum, BDD, and Kanban project experience.</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="timeline">Timeline</h1>
<h2 id="service-based-work">Service-based Work</h2>
<h3 id="accessibility-specialist-at-jaffamonkey-ltd">Accessibility Specialist at jaffamonkey Ltd</h3>
<p>Providing Accessibility audit service for startups following compliance process, covering web and mobile apps. Clients are mostly health app startups who are following compliance requirements required for NHS approval. The audit consists of manual and automated activities commonly covering WCAG 2.2 Level AA (alongside UAAG 2.0 for additional mobile-specific coverage). I also provide clients with tools such as screenreader test automation and CI (a11y) tool integrations, with ready-to-go full setups, along with a final Accessibility Statement.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 1: A multi-tenant platform to collaborate and create/share content with partners and stakeholders across different healthcare organisations.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 2: Established service that develops products and services to make life easier for people with deeply personal and private medical conditions.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 3: An AI medical technology company dedicated to developing AI medical products intended for disease screening and diagnosis, disease intervention and treatment, patient management and medical research, for full-hospital deployment serving physicians from multiple departments.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 4: A health service offering online consultations and home health-testing services and non-NHS medical letters – removing the need for a GP appointment.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 5 A CQC-regulated fully online chronic pain clinic, offering evidence-based treatments for chronic pain (including those not available on the NHS, including medical cannabis).</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>Client 6: A software enables businesses and organisations with complex workflow needs to efficiently store, manage, distribute, and re-use digital files.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="contract-work">Contract Work</h2>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-bet365">Lead SDET at bet365</h3>
<p>December 2022 — October 2023</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Rework of Android app and new iOS app version</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Test framework proofs of concept for UI/API testing for Android, iOS and Web apps (migration from Appium/Selenium frameworks)</li>
<li>Espresso/Kotlin test framework &amp; test development</li>
<li>iOS Swift/XCUITest test framework &amp; test development</li>
<li>Skills transfer to test teams</li>
<li>Bash shell script development for ease of build test setup and test run on local device or Saucelabs device cloud.</li>
<li>Azure pipeline development for CI test runs and reporting.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-and-quality-assurance-at-ceta-insurance-ltd">Lead SDET and Quality Assurance at Ceta Insurance Ltd</h3>
<p>January 2022 — September 2022</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Major refactoring web projects across the Ceta Insurance brand</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>High level test automation strategies</li>
<li>Test framework PoC and implementation for UI and API testing (Cucumber/Playwright and RestSharp frameworks)</li>
<li>Load/Performance test and monitoring framework development for Production sites.</li>
<li>Azure pipeline development for CI test runs and reporting.</li>
<li>Support for Scrummaster on introducing Agile processes, including the business side.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="lead-sdetbdd-strategist-at-cgi">Lead SDET/BDD Strategist at CGI</h3>
<p>November 2020 — October 2021</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: BDD-driven project for a Flutter-based banking app, utilising &ldquo;Backend for Frontend&rdquo; (BFF) to organize the microservice architectures and coordinate functionality across the system (including third-party API&rsquo;s).</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Lead SDET across 4 Scrum teams.</li>
<li>Test framework PoC and implementation</li>
<li>High level test automation strategies for App (Flutter/Dart) and API (C#) testing in BDD context</li>
<li>JMeter framework for API Load testing with extensive reporting.</li>
<li>Flutter Driver/Dart test framework architecture and implementation.</li>
<li>C#/Specflow/RestSharp test framework architecture and implementation.</li>
<li>Extensive use of Bash scripts and Azure pipelines to streamline the testing process.</li>
<li>Service virtualization of third-party API&rsquo;s.</li>
<li>Implementing continuous testing in the CI pipeline.</li>
<li>Setup of BitBar cloud device testing</li>
<li>Leading app testing effort across teams</li>
<li>Mentoring  test engineers</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="quality-assurance-specialist-at-doccoms">Quality Assurance Specialist at DocComs</h3>
<p>April 2020 — August 2020</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Mobile app startup project, aimed at improving communication between doctors about patients.</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Responsible for overall Quality assurance</li>
<li>Coding API and App UI test frameworks for testing Android and iOS version of app (C#/Appium/XCUITest/XCTest).</li>
<li>Browserstack integration for cross-device testing.</li>
<li>API load testing using JMeter</li>
<li>Implementing SonarQube for code-level security testing.</li>
<li>Implementing Specflow as part of drive towards BDD approach.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-engine--transformation">Lead SDET at Engine | Transformation</h3>
<p>June 2019 — October 2019</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: A feature-rich civil service training and career development web and mobile app (Ruby-on-Rails).</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-ai-quality-engineer-at-tele2">Lead AI Quality Engineer at Tele2</h3>
<p>September 2018 — March 2019</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Custom Mobile AI Chatbot, developed with Python and using the IBM Watson service.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-transform-uk">Lead SDET at Transform UK</h3>
<p>June 2017 — July 2018</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Drupal/NodeJS app to manage partnerships between businesses and local authorities.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-i2n">Lead SDET at i2N</h3>
<p>December 2016 — April 2017</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: AngularJS web/mobile application to manage nationwide young offender placements.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-transform-uk-1">Lead SDET at Transform UK</h3>
<p>June 2016 — December 2016</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Java/AngularJS application for NHS Training and Education management system.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-wowcher">Lead SDET at Wowcher</h3>
<p>January 2016 — April 2016</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: AngularJS/Node app for voucher management and sales.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-tnt-netherlands">Lead SDET at TNT (Netherlands),</h3>
<p>July 2015 — November 2015</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: AngularJS web app aimed at improving user experience for TNT customers.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-hiveworks">Lead SDET at Hiveworks</h3>
<p>March 2015 — June 2015</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Drupal/Node/ElasticSearch CMS web application, aimed at providing content for external users, and means to manage content for Orange brand teams.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-transform-uk-2">Lead SDET at Transform UK</h3>
<p>December 2015 — March 2015</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Symfony2 (PHP) application for a Civil Service Resourcing job application management.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="lead-sdet-at-transform-uk-3">Lead SDET at Transform UK</h3>
<p>September 2013 — November 2014</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: PHP/AngularJS application for OPG (Office of the Public Guardian) case and task management system, for customers seeking power of attorney.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="test-manager-at-kpmg">Test Manager at KPMG</h3>
<p>April 2011 — December 2012</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: Multiple C# web-based tax, finance and public sector projects.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="test-manager-at-digital-jigsaw">Test Manager at Digital Jigsaw</h3>
<p>February 2011 — April 2011</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Project: MyVodafone customer account app (with dynamic hotspot locator/connector) for Android, iPhone and Blackberry.</p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>Employment history 1997-2010 is available upon request</em></p>
<h1 id="technical-skills">Technical skills</h1>
<h2 id="programming-languages">Programming languages</h2>
<p>Python, Kotlin, TypeScript, JavaScript, C#, Java, Swift, Bash, PHP, Ruby</p>
<h2 id="test-frameworks">Test frameworks</h2>
<p>Jest, Cucumber, Nightwatch, Behave, Protractor, Behat, JUnit, Jasmine, WebdriverIO, CasparJS, PHPUnit, Mink, Fitnesse, Selenium, Playwright.</p>
<h2 id="mobile-test-frameworks">Mobile test frameworks</h2>
<p>Appium, Flutter Driver, XCUITest, XCTest, Calabash, Browserstack, Kobiton, Xamarin UITests, Espresso.</p>
<h2 id="other-test-tools">Other Test Tools</h2>
<p>JMeter, Artillery, OWASP ZAP, Pa11y, Superagent</p>
<h2 id="devops">DevOps</h2>
<p>Azure, AWS, TravisCI, Jenkins, GitHub, BitBucket, TFS, VMWare, VirtualBox, Docker, Vagrant</p>
<h2 id="development-frameworks">Development frameworks</h2>
<p>Dart, Ruby on Rails, Angular, Node, React, Spring, Drupal, Symfony2, Zend2, MVC</p>
<h1 id="qualifications">Qualifications</h1>
<p>BTEC HND Computing (Prince, SSADM, C++, COBOL, Computer Architecture, Business Analysis)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Engineering</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_qualityengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_qualityengineering/</guid>
      <description>Bringing quality to all aspects of a project.&#xA;Primary benefits of Quality Engineering Quality assurance and testing across the SDLC. Helping teams standardize the application of quality requirement. Adopt tooling to increase the efficiency of the process. Automating tests to eliminate issues related to manual testing. Integrating testing into CI/CD pipelines. Test development in line with development cycle. Every test should be able to provide the same answer of &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo;, at any point, to the question &amp;ldquo;Are you useful?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>Bringing quality to all aspects of a project.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="primary-benefits-of-quality-engineering">Primary benefits of Quality Engineering</h2>
<ul>
<li>Quality assurance and testing across the SDLC.</li>
<li>Helping teams standardize the application of quality requirement.</li>
<li>Adopt tooling to increase the efficiency of the process.</li>
<li>Automating tests to eliminate issues related to manual testing.</li>
<li>Integrating testing into CI/CD pipelines.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="test-development-in-line-with-development-cycle">Test development in line with development cycle.</h2>
<ul>
<li>Every test should be able to provide the same answer of &ldquo;Yes&rdquo;, at any point, to the question &ldquo;Are you useful?&rdquo;.</li>
<li>Starting lean with test framework is logical, wait for test developmemnt to highlight possible requirement.</li>
<li>Native tools always preferred, firstly for synergy with development and secondly performance and scope larger.</li>
<li>Test frameworks should be part of app codebase.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://calendly.com/jaffamonkeyltd/intro-call">Book an intro meeting</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_services/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility WCAG Level A Audit Web Windows Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check Mac Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mobile iOS Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check Android Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check WCAG Level AA Audit Web Windows NVDA check Follow User Guide Record session Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mac VoiceOver check Follow User Guide Record session Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mobile iOS VoiceOver check Follow User Guide Record session Code Check (SonarQube) Access to codebase Yes No Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Android TalkBack check Follow User Guide Record session Code Check (SonarQube) Access to codebase Yes No Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Tools Self-hosted Browser based automation to return screenreader output</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 id="accessibility">Accessibility</h1>
<h2 id="wcag-level">WCAG Level</h2>
<h3 id="a">A</h3>
<ul>
<li>Audit
<ul>
<li>Web
<ul>
<li>Windows
<ul>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
<li>UX Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Mac
<ul>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
<li></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Mobile
<ul>
<li>iOS
<ul>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
<li>UX Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Android
<ul>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
<li>UX Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="wcag-level-1">WCAG Level</h2>
<h3 id="aa">AA</h3>
<ul>
<li>Audit
<ul>
<li>Web
<ul>
<li>Windows
<ul>
<li>NVDA check
<ul>
<li>Follow User Guide</li>
<li>Record session</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Mac
<ul>
<li>VoiceOver check
<ul>
<li>Follow User Guide</li>
<li>Record session</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Mobile
<ul>
<li>iOS
<ul>
<li>VoiceOver check
<ul>
<li>Follow User Guide</li>
<li>Record session</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Code Check (SonarQube)
<ul>
<li>Access to codebase
<ul>
<li>Yes</li>
<li>No</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Android
<ul>
<li>TalkBack check
<ul>
<li>Follow User Guide</li>
<li>Record session</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Code Check (SonarQube)
<ul>
<li>Access to codebase
<ul>
<li>Yes</li>
<li>No</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Color Contrast Check
<ul>
<li>(Part of tools check)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test Resize Check</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="tools">Tools</h2>
<h3 id="self-hosted">Self-hosted</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Browser based automation to return screenreader output</p>
<ul>
<li>Test Framework
<ul>
<li>Cypress
<ul>
<li>Add a11y/axe package</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Cucumber
<ul>
<li>Add a11y/axe package</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Jest
<ul>
<li>Add a11y/axe package</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Web-based dashboard</p>
<ul>
<li>Login barrier
<ul>
<li>Yes
<ul>
<li>Login barrier
<ul>
<li>Add login script</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Add urls to dashboard</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<ul>
<li>Add urls to dashboard</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>SonarQube code check</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Pa11y/Axe scanning tool</p>
<ul>
<li>Login barrier
<ul>
<li>Yes
<ul>
<li>Login barrier
<ul>
<li>Add login script</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Sitemap?
<ul>
<li>Yes
<ul>
<li>Add url</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>No
<ul>
<li>Add urls to list</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<ul>
<li>Sitemap?
- Yes<br>
- Add url<br>
- No<br>
- Add urls to list</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Lighthouse check</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="strategy">Strategy</h2>
<h3 id="things-to-check-regards-design">Things to check regards Design</h3>
<ul>
<li>Check color contrast</li>
<li>Check behaviour on resize</li>
<li>Check forms in detail</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="things-to-check-regards-development">Things to check regards Development</h3>
<ul>
<li>Build server
<ul>
<li>Azure
<ul>
<li>Add plugins
<ul>
<li>SonarQubbe</li>
<li>Pa11y Ci/Axe Scan</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Jenkins
<ul>
<li>Add plugins
<ul>
<li>SonarQubbe</li>
<li>Pa11y Ci/Axe Scan</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Gitlab
<ul>
<li>Add plugins
<ul>
<li>SonarQubbe</li>
<li>Pa11y Ci/Axe Scan</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Build cycle
<ul>
<li>Run CLI tool with each build</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test adhoc with browser add-ons
<ul>
<li>HTML Sniffer</li>
<li>Tota11y</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Test adhoc with mobile apps
<ul>
<li>ANDROID:App Accessibility Scanner Checker</li>
<li>ANDROID: AXE App Accessibility Checker</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="disabilities-to-consider-regards-ux">Disabilities to consider regards UX</h3>
<ul>
<li>Autistic spectrum</li>
<li>Dyslexia</li>
<li>Age</li>
<li>Language</li>
<li>Culture</li>
<li>Education</li>
<li>Economic position</li>
<li>Technological aptitude</li>
<li>Cognitive</li>
<li>Physical Mobility</li>
<li>Auditory</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Strategy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_teststrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_teststrategy/</guid>
      <description>Development strategies to help you implement new tools and approaches across teams. Building test frameworks for functional and non-functional testing within your CI/CD pipelines.&#xA;Bringing quality to all aspects of a project.&#xA;25 years providing quality services on well over 100 projects, for 60+ clients. I can bring a wealth of technical skills expertise, along with delivering quality improvements to project pipeline - even on projects considered unrescuable.&#xA;Book an intro meeting</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Development strategies to help you implement new tools and approaches across teams.
Building test frameworks for functional and non-functional testing within your CI/CD pipelines.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Bringing quality to all aspects of a project.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>25 years providing quality services on well over 100 projects, for 60+ clients. I can bring a wealth of technical skills expertise, along with delivering quality improvements to project pipeline - even on projects considered unrescuable.</p>
<p><a href="https://calendly.com/jaffamonkeyltd/intro-call">Book an intro meeting</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site performance</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_thissite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_thissite/</guid>
      <description>This site has privacy and accessibility built in. It&amp;rsquo;s also compatible with modern security standards.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This site has <a href="https://themarkup.org/blacklight?url=jaffamonkey.com">privacy</a> and <a href="https://pagespeed.web.dev/report?url=https%3A%2F%2Fjaffamonkey.com">accessibility</a> built in. It&rsquo;s also compatible with modern <a href="https://github.com/clente/hugo-bearcub#secure">security</a> standards.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCAG 4 Principles</title>
      <link>https://example.org/_wcagprinciples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_wcagprinciples/</guid>
      <description>In order for your web or mobile app to be accessible, the audience needs to be factored into the design and development.&#xA;people with sight loss, low vision or who use a screen reader those with colour deficiencies or colour blindness people with hearing loss or who are deaf those with limited dexterity those with learning difficulties, like dyslexia, those who are autistic or have ADHD What are the four principles of content accessibility (POUR)?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In order for your web or mobile app to be accessible, the audience needs to be factored into the design and development.</p>
<ul>
<li>people with sight loss, low vision or who use a screen reader</li>
<li>those with colour deficiencies or colour blindness
people with hearing loss or who are deaf</li>
<li>those with limited dexterity</li>
<li>those with learning difficulties, like dyslexia, those who are autistic or have ADHD</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p>What are the four principles of content accessibility (POUR)?</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Perceivable</li>
<li>Operable</li>
<li>Understandable</li>
<li>Robust</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="perceivable">Perceivable</h1>
<h2 id="relevant-senses">Relevant senses</h2>
<ul>
<li>sight</li>
<li>hearing</li>
<li>touch
The content on your website needs to be perceivable to at least one of the senses.</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="operable">Operable</h1>
<p>There are many different ways that people might interact with your website.</p>
<ul>
<li>keyboard navigation</li>
<li>screen reader</li>
<li>speech recognition software.</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="understandable">Understandable</h1>
<p>People with dyslexia can struggle with reading and lots of text. Others on the autism spectrum, can struggle with metaphorical and figurative language.</p>
<h2 id="a-general-guide">A general guide</h2>
<ul>
<li>shorter sentences, Hemingway App can help</li>
<li>remove jargon or complex language</li>
<li>break up long paragraphs</li>
<li>headings to break up long pages</li>
<li>short bullet points</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="robust">Robust</h1>
<p>Is your website built in a way that is compatible with the technology of your audience?
Can visually impaired people use a screen reader to access the content on your website?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.</p>
<h2 id="headings">Headings</h2>
<p>The following HTML <code>&lt;h1&gt;</code>—<code>&lt;h6&gt;</code> elements represent six levels of section headings. <code>&lt;h1&gt;</code> is the highest section level while <code>&lt;h6&gt;</code> is the lowest.</p>
<h1 id="h1">H1</h1>
<h2 id="h2">H2</h2>
<h3 id="h3">H3</h3>
<h4 id="h4">H4</h4>
<h5 id="h5">H5</h5>
<h6 id="h6">H6</h6>
<h2 id="paragraph">Paragraph</h2>
<p>Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga. Ri oditatquam, ad quibus unda veliamenimin cusam et facea ipsamus es exerum sitate dolores editium rerore eost, temped molorro ratiae volorro te reribus dolorer sperchicium faceata tiustia prat.</p>
<p>Itatur? Quiatae cullecum rem ent aut odis in re eossequodi nonsequ idebis ne sapicia is sinveli squiatum, core et que aut hariosam ex eat.</p>
<h2 id="blockquotes">Blockquotes</h2>
<p>The blockquote element represents content that is quoted from another source, optionally with a citation which must be within a <code>footer</code> or <code>cite</code> element, and optionally with in-line changes such as annotations and abbreviations.</p>
<h4 id="blockquote-without-attribution">Blockquote without attribution</h4>
<blockquote>
<p>Tiam, ad mint andaepu dandae nostion secatur sequo quae.
<strong>Note</strong> that you can use <em>Markdown syntax</em> within a blockquote.</p>
</blockquote>
<h4 id="blockquote-with-attribution">Blockquote with attribution</h4>
<blockquote>
<p>Don&rsquo;t communicate by sharing memory, share memory by communicating.<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
— <!-- raw HTML omitted -->Rob Pike<sup id="fnref:1"><a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1</a></sup><!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="tables">Tables</h2>
<p>Tables aren&rsquo;t part of the core Markdown spec, but Hugo supports supports them out-of-the-box.</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Age</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Bob</td>
<td>27</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Alice</td>
<td>23</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h4 id="inline-markdown-within-tables">Inline Markdown within tables</h4>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Italics</th>
<th>Bold</th>
<th>Code</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><em>italics</em></td>
<td><strong>bold</strong></td>
<td><code>code</code></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2 id="code-blocks">Code Blocks</h2>
<h4 id="code-block-with-backticks">Code block with backticks</h4>





<div class="highlight"><pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;"><code class="language-html" data-lang="html"><span style="display:flex;"><span><span style="color:#75715e">&lt;!doctype html&gt;</span>
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">html</span> <span style="color:#a6e22e">lang</span><span style="color:#f92672">=</span><span style="color:#e6db74">&#34;en&#34;</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">head</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">meta</span> <span style="color:#a6e22e">charset</span><span style="color:#f92672">=</span><span style="color:#e6db74">&#34;utf-8&#34;</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">title</span>&gt;Example HTML5 Document&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">title</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">head</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">body</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">p</span>&gt;Test&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">p</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">body</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">html</span>&gt;</span></span></code></pre></div><h4 id="code-block-indented-with-four-spaces">Code block indented with four spaces</h4>
<pre><code>&lt;!doctype html&gt;
&lt;html lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
  &lt;meta charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;
  &lt;title&gt;Example HTML5 Document&lt;/title&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Test&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
</code></pre>
<h4 id="code-block-with-hugos-internal-highlight-shortcode">Code block with Hugo&rsquo;s internal highlight shortcode</h4>




<div class="highlight"><pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;"><code class="language-html" data-lang="html"><span style="display:flex;"><span><span style="color:#75715e">&lt;!doctype html&gt;</span>
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">html</span> <span style="color:#a6e22e">lang</span><span style="color:#f92672">=</span><span style="color:#e6db74">&#34;en&#34;</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">head</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">meta</span> <span style="color:#a6e22e">charset</span><span style="color:#f92672">=</span><span style="color:#e6db74">&#34;utf-8&#34;</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">title</span>&gt;Example HTML5 Document&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">title</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">head</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;<span style="color:#f92672">body</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  &lt;<span style="color:#f92672">p</span>&gt;Test&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">p</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">body</span>&gt;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>&lt;/<span style="color:#f92672">html</span>&gt;</span></span></code></pre></div>
<h2 id="list-types">List Types</h2>
<h4 id="ordered-list">Ordered List</h4>
<ol>
<li>First item</li>
<li>Second item</li>
<li>Third item</li>
</ol>
<h4 id="unordered-list">Unordered List</h4>
<ul>
<li>List item</li>
<li>Another item</li>
<li>And another item</li>
</ul>
<h4 id="nested-list">Nested list</h4>
<ul>
<li>Fruit
<ul>
<li>Apple</li>
<li>Orange</li>
<li>Banana</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Dairy
<ul>
<li>Milk</li>
<li>Cheese</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="other-elements--abbr-sub-sup-kbd-mark">Other Elements — abbr, sub, sup, kbd, mark</h2>
<p><!-- raw HTML omitted -->GIF<!-- raw HTML omitted --> is a bitmap image format.</p>
<p>H<!-- raw HTML omitted -->2<!-- raw HTML omitted -->O</p>
<p>X<!-- raw HTML omitted -->n<!-- raw HTML omitted --> + Y<!-- raw HTML omitted -->n<!-- raw HTML omitted --> = Z<!-- raw HTML omitted -->n<!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
<p>Press <!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted -->CTRL<!-- raw HTML omitted -->+<!-- raw HTML omitted -->ALT<!-- raw HTML omitted -->+<!-- raw HTML omitted -->Delete<!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --> to end the session.</p>
<p>Most <!-- raw HTML omitted -->salamanders<!-- raw HTML omitted --> are nocturnal, and hunt for insects, worms, and other small creatures.</p>
<div class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes">
<hr>
<ol>
<li id="fn:1">
<p>The above quote is excerpted from Rob Pike&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAAkCSZUG1c">talk</a> during Gopherfest, November 18, 2015.&#160;<a href="#fnref:1" class="footnote-backref" role="doc-backlink">&#x21a9;&#xfe0e;</a></p>
</li>
</ol>
</div>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hugo ships with several <a href="https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes">Built-in Shortcodes</a> for rich content, along with a <a href="https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/">Privacy Config</a> and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="youtube-privacy-enhanced-shortcode">YouTube Privacy Enhanced Shortcode</h2>

<div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
  <iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZJthWmvUzzc" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" allowfullscreen title="YouTube Video"></iframe>
</div>

<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<hr>
<h2 id="twitter-simple-shortcode">Twitter Simple Shortcode</h2>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">“In addition to being more logical, asymmetry has the advantage that its complete appearance is far more optically effective than symmetry.”<br>— Jan Tschichold <a href="https://t.co/gcv7SrhvJb">pic.twitter.com/gcv7SrhvJb</a></p>&mdash; Design Reviewed | Graphic Design History (@DesignReviewed) <a href="https://twitter.com/DesignReviewed/status/1085870671291310081?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 17, 2019</a></blockquote>
<script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>


<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<hr>
<h2 id="vimeo-simple-shortcode">Vimeo Simple Shortcode</h2>






<style>
.__h_video {
   position: relative;
   padding-bottom: 56.23%;
   height: 0;
   overflow: hidden;
   width: 100%;
   background: #000;
}
.__h_video img {
   width: 100%;
   height: auto;
   color: #000;
}
.__h_video .play {
   height: 72px;
   width: 72px;
   left: 50%;
   top: 50%;
   margin-left: -36px;
   margin-top: -36px;
   position: absolute;
   cursor: pointer;
}
</style>


<div class="s_video_simple __h_video">
<a href="https://vimeo.com/4.8912912e&#43;07" rel="noopener" target="_blank">


<img src="https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640" srcset="https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640 1x, https://i.vimeocdn.com/video/337401969-979f0cc9f55fdf305fb8984e90d92639ec9d7ecc4c9dfbc6536e28edb43784ce-d_640 2x" alt="Sing Jan Swing - Kinetic Type">
<div class="play"><svg version="1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewBox="0 0 61 61"><circle cx="30.5" cy="30.5" r="30.5" opacity=".8" fill="#000"></circle><path d="M25.3 19.2c-2.1-1.2-3.8-.2-3.8 2.2v18.1c0 2.4 1.7 3.4 3.8 2.2l16.6-9.1c2.1-1.2 2.1-3.2 0-4.4l-16.6-9z" fill="#fff"></path></svg></div></a></div>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.</p>
<p>Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc caluere tempus inhospita parcite confusaque translucet patri vestro qui optatis lumine cognoscere flos nubis! Fronde ipsamque patulos Dryopen deorum.</p>
<ol>
<li>Exierant elisi ambit vivere dedere</li>
<li>Duce pollice</li>
<li>Eris modo</li>
<li>Spargitque ferrea quos palude</li>
</ol>
<p>Rursus nulli murmur; hastile inridet ut ab gravi sententia! Nomine potitus silentia flumen, sustinet placuit petis in dilapsa erat sunt. Atria tractus malis.</p>
<ol>
<li>Comas hunc haec pietate fetum procerum dixit</li>
<li>Post torum vates letum Tiresia</li>
<li>Flumen querellas</li>
<li>Arcanaque montibus omnes</li>
<li>Quidem et</li>
</ol>
<h1 id="vagus-elidunt">Vagus elidunt</h1>
<p><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --><!-- raw HTML omitted --></p>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canons_of_page_construction#Van_de_Graaf_canon">The Van de Graaf Canon</a></p>
<h2 id="mane-refeci-capiebant-unda-mulcebat">Mane refeci capiebant unda mulcebat</h2>
<p>Victa caducifer, malo vulnere contra dicere aurato, ludit regale, voca! Retorsit colit est profanae esse virescere furit nec; iaculi matertera et visa est, viribus. Divesque creatis, tecta novat collumque vulnus est, parvas. <strong>Faces illo pepulere</strong> tempus adest. Tendit flamma, ab opes virum sustinet, sidus sequendo urbis.</p>
<p>Iubar proles corpore raptos vero auctor imperium; sed et huic: manus caeli Lelegas tu lux. Verbis obstitit intus oblectamina fixis linguisque ausus sperare Echionides cornuaque tenent clausit possit. Omnia putatur. Praeteritae refert ausus; ferebant e primus lora nutat, vici quae mea ipse. Et iter nil spectatae vulnus haerentia iuste et exercebat, sui et.</p>
<p>Eurytus Hector, materna ipsumque ut Politen, nec, nate, ignari, vernum cohaesit sequitur. Vel <strong>mitis temploque</strong> vocatus, inque alis, <em>oculos nomen</em> non silvis corpore coniunx ne displicet illa. Crescunt non unus, vidit visa quantum inmiti flumina mortis facto sic: undique a alios vincula sunt iactata abdita! Suspenderat ego fuit tendit: luna, ante urbem Propoetides <strong>parte</strong>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.</p>
<p>In this example we will be using <a href="https://katex.org/">KaTeX</a></p>
<ul>
<li>Create a partial under <code>/layouts/partials/math.html</code></li>
<li>Within this partial reference the <a href="https://katex.org/docs/autorender.html">Auto-render Extension</a> or host these scripts locally.</li>
<li>Include the partial in your templates like so:</li>
</ul>





<div class="highlight"><pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;"><code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"><span style="display:flex;"><span><span style="color:#f92672">{{</span> <span style="color:#66d9ef">if</span> or .Params.math .Site.Params.math <span style="color:#f92672">}}</span>
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span><span style="color:#f92672">{{</span> partial <span style="color:#e6db74">&#34;math.html&#34;</span> . <span style="color:#f92672">}}</span>
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span><span style="color:#f92672">{{</span> end <span style="color:#f92672">}}</span></span></span></code></pre></div><ul>
<li>To enable KaTex globally set the parameter <code>math</code> to <code>true</code> in a project&rsquo;s configuration</li>
<li>To enable KaTex on a per page basis include the parameter <code>math: true</code> in content files</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Note:</strong> Use the online reference of <a href="https://katex.org/docs/supported.html">Supported TeX Functions</a></p>

<h3 id="examples">Examples</h3>

<p>Block math:
$$
\varphi = 1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\frac{1} {1+\cdots} } }
$$</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://gohugo.io/functions/emojify/"><code>emojify</code></a> function can be called directly in templates or <a href="https://gohugo.io/templates/shortcode-templates/#inline-shortcodes">Inline Shortcodes</a>.</p>
<p>To enable emoji globally, set <code>enableEmoji</code> to <code>true</code> in your site&rsquo;s <a href="https://gohugo.io/getting-started/configuration/">configuration</a> and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.</p>
<!-- raw HTML omitted -->
<p>The <a href="http://www.emoji-cheat-sheet.com/">Emoji cheat sheet</a> is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>N.B.</strong> The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform. To style the emoji you can either use a third party emoji font or a font stack; e.g.</p>




<div class="highlight"><pre tabindex="0" style="color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;"><code class="language-html" data-lang="html"><span style="display:flex;"><span>.emoji {
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>  font-family: Apple Color Emoji, Segoe UI Emoji, NotoColorEmoji, Segoe UI Symbol, Android Emoji, EmojiSymbols;
</span></span><span style="display:flex;"><span>}</span></span></code></pre></div>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/_choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/_choices/</guid>
      <description>Web Windows/MacOS All content Content by template Sitemap or Urls list (Level AA only) Screenreader Automation (Level AA only) Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Supply user guide Manual testing Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Design &amp;amp; UX UX Testing + (Level AA only) Disabilities &amp;amp; UX (Level AA only) ** Manual screenreader checks (Level AA only) Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Login Required?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 id="web">Web</h3>
<ul>
<li>Windows/MacOS
<ul>
<li>All content
Content by template
<ul>
<li>Sitemap or Urls list
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Screenreader Automation
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>NVDA
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Supply user guide
<ul>
<li>Manual testing
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>NVDA
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Design &amp; UX</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>UX Testing +
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Disabilities &amp; UX
(<em>Level AA only</em>) **</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Manual screenreader checks
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>NVDA
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Login Required?
<ul>
<li>Supply Login URL
<ul>
<li>Extract login script</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>DevOps
<ul>
<li>Run SonarQube
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Sitemap or Urls list
<ul>
<li>Pa11y CI</li>
<li>AxeScan</li>
<li>Pa11y Dashboard</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Build Server
<ul>
<li>SonarQube Plugin
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>a11y plugins</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mobile-web">Mobile Web</h3>
<ul>
<li>Android/iOS
<ul>
<li>All content<br>
Content by template
<ul>
<li>Sitemap or Urls list
<ul>
<li>Screenreader Automation
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>NVDA
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Supply user guide
<ul>
<li>Manual testing
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>TalkBack
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Design &amp; UX</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>UX Testing +
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Disabilities &amp; UX
(<em>Level AA only</em>) **</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Manual screenreader checks
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>TalkBack
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Login Required?
<ul>
<li>Supply Login URL
<ul>
<li>Extract login script</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>DevOps
<ul>
<li>Run SonarQube
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Sitemap or Urls list
<ul>
<li>Pa11y CI</li>
<li>
<h2 id="axescan">AxeScan</h2>
</li>
<li>Pa11y Dashboard</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Build Server
<ul>
<li>SonarQube Plugin
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>a11y plugins</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="mobile-app">Mobile App</h3>
<ul>
<li>Android/iOS
<ul>
<li>All content<br>
Content by template
<ul>
<li>Supply user guide
<ul>
<li>Manual testing
<ul>
<li>Voiceover
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>TalkBack
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Design &amp; UX</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>UX Testing
(<em>Level AA only</em>)
<ul>
<li>Disabilities &amp; UX
(<em>Level AA only</em>) **</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Login Required?
<ul>
<li>Supply Login details</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>DevOps
<ul>
<li>Run SonarQube
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
<li>Build Server
<ul>
<li>SonarQube Plugin
(<em>Level AA only</em>)</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Mobile tools check
<ul>
<li>Android</li>
<li>iOS</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>** <em>Disabilities: Dyslexia, Age, Language, Culture, Education, Economic position, Tech aptitude, Cognitive, Physical Mobility, Auditory.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
