<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>quality engineering in the pipeline</title>
    <link>https://example.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on quality engineering in the pipeline</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_accessibilitystrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_accessibilitystrategy/</guid>
      <description>Understanding why accessibility makes you a better and smarter organisation is the first step in any long-term strategy.&#xA;What are advantage of integrating Accessibility into your design and development practices.&#xA;Drive Innovation Accessibility features in products and services often solve unanticipated problems.&#xA;Enhance Your Brand Diversity and inclusion efforts so important to business success are accelerated with a clear, well-integrated accessibility commitment.&#xA;Extend Market Reach The global market of people with disabilities is over 1 billion people with a spending power of more than $6 trillion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_autism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_autism/</guid>
      <description>Autism is a spectrum. Not everyone who is autistic prefers the same things. Many autistic people also have associated other conditions, like Dyslexia or Learning Difficulties thatimpact on their preferences. Many do not have other conditions. Other demographic factors can also impact people’s references, such as socio economic factors, and familiarity with technology.&#xA;These differences can make it challenging to design for all autistic web users, and below is a general guide to assist in those challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_choices/</guid>
      <description>With a simple set of choices, we can run accessibility tests in our pipelines and generate useful feedback for your development design teams.&#xA;While manual checks are always recommended, you can achieve a high degree of prevention by introducing automation into your design and development cycles.&#xA;Web Windows/MacOS All content Content by template Sitemap or Urls list (Level AA only) Screenreader Automation (Level AA only) Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Supply user guide Manual testing Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Design &amp;amp; UX UX Testing + (Level AA only) Disabilities &amp;amp; UX (Level AA only) ** Manual screenreader checks (Level AA only) Voiceover (Level AA only) NVDA (Level AA only) Login Required?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_history/</guid>
      <description>Download Word Version&#xA;I combine the disciplines of test engineering, DevOps, exploratory testing, test management and quality assurance to provide a more rounded contribution than simply testing. 10 years total commercial experience of building test frameworks and coding API, UI and performance tests. Ensuring maximum value, by implementing tests in CI/CD pipelines. Expertise in challenging environments, and contributing improvements to the process of achieving testing goals and objectives. Frequently involved in DevOps and business decisions, and have mentored both technical and business members of team, to engage more with the quality process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_services/</guid>
      <description>Accessibility WCAG Level A Audit Web Windows Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check Mac Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mobile iOS Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check Android Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check UX Check WCAG Level AA Audit Web Windows NVDA check Follow User Guide Record session Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mac VoiceOver check Follow User Guide Record session Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Mobile iOS VoiceOver check Follow User Guide Record session Code Check (SonarQube) Access to codebase Yes No Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Android TalkBack check Follow User Guide Record session Code Check (SonarQube) Access to codebase Yes No Color Contrast Check (Part of tools check) Test Resize Check Tools Self-hosted Browser based automation to return screenreader output</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_teststrategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_teststrategy/</guid>
      <description>Development strategies to help you implement new tools and approaches across teams. Building test frameworks for functional and non-functional testing within your CI/CD pipelines.&#xA;Bringing quality to all aspects of a project.&#xA;25 years providing quality services on well over 100 projects, for 60+ clients. I can bring a wealth of technical skills expertise, along with delivering quality improvements to project pipeline - even on projects considered unrescuable.&#xA;Book an intro meeting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_thissite/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_thissite/</guid>
      <description>This site has privacy and accessibility built in. It&amp;rsquo;s also compatible with modern security standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.org/blog/_wcagprinciples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/blog/_wcagprinciples/</guid>
      <description>In order for your web or mobile app to be accessible, the audience needs to be factored into the design and development.&#xA;people with sight loss, low vision or who use a screen reader those with colour deficiencies or colour blindness people with hearing loss or who are deaf those with limited dexterity those with learning difficulties, like dyslexia, those who are autistic or have ADHD What are the four principles of content accessibility (POUR)?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
